Dahee Lee

Toronto, ON | 647-207-0055 | DHL99270@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I am a solutions-driven full stack developer who is passionate about user experience and accessibility. I have over 7 years of front-facing customer service experience and am confident in delivering solutions to resolve customer concerns by collaborating and communicating effectively with others. Being part of a team to help design, develop, and test products that meet user's needs and wants would be an exciting opportunity for me.

TECHNICAL & INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, EJS

Libraries and Frameworks: Express.js, Django, React, Bootstrap, Tailwind

Databases and other: MongoDB, Mongoose, PostgreSQL, RESTful Routing, JSON API, GitHub

Interpersonal skills: Communication and Listening skills, Teamwork, Conflict-resolution

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Places - GitHub | App - JavaScript | Express | PostgreSQL | React

Places is an app where users can create property listings and manage these listings.

- Designed a dynamic search bar that filters results
- Implemented a PostgreSQL database for maintaining data in the backend server
- Created an engaging and responsive user interface with React

Pens - GitHub | App - JavaScript | EJS | Mongoose

Pens is an app where users can create, update, and delete diary-like entries

- RESTful routes and app functionality using Express.js, mongoDB and Mongoose
- CSS and animations used to create a soft colour palette them

Good Start - GitHub | App - Javascript | HTML | CSS

Good Start helps busy users stop and start their day with an inspiring quote and meditative colour animation

- Built a function to retrieve API data to display inspirational quotes
- Created a glowing, animated background with CSS

EXPERIENCE

Salesperson, Home Standards Brickstone Realty

Toronto, ON, 01/2020 - Present

Represented Toronto based clients in residential purchases and sales, leases, and pre-construction purchases

- Improved sales revenue by 250%
- Negotiated a reduction in purchase price by 30% of expected market value for a client
- Completed successful deal transactions for over 25 clients
- Managed client listings and assisted clients with using electronic tools such as BrokerBay and Authentisign

Customer Service and Sales Representative, Air Canada

Toronto, ON, 08/2016 - Present

Provide an excellent customer service experience to Air Canada passengers

- Accurately processed customer bookings with personal information and documents
- Promoted for a special projects team to deliver timely resolutions for customer issues
- Achieved average sales of \$700+ per hour by listening to and identifying customer needs

Digital Marketing Manager, Golden Voice Online Education

Toronto, ON, 07/2015 - 07/2016

Managed the company's digital platforms, including content creation, advertising, and media pitching

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Remote, Certificate Expected: 12/2023

Full-stack software engineering program (420+ hours) focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies.

University of Toronto, Honours Bachelor of Arts, Human Geography and Political Science

Toronto, ON, 05/2015